truegether.com 2019-05-06

# TrueGether: Privacy Policy

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for TrueGether.com website. You accept this policy when you visit TrueGether.com.

Information Collection and Use

TrueGether.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We value your trust and we will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.

Web Site Registration

You can browse our website without registering. We will determine your nearest city based on your ip address but you will remain completely anonymous to us.

In order to use some features of this Web site, users need to login using an identity provider like Facebook, LinkedIn or Google. These providers give us your fullname and email address. We do not have access to your google or linkedin password. This information is used to contact users about the listings or other information on our site relevant to them. This information is also used to display relevant information ( like recently listed items in your network or in your neighbourhood )to the user. It is optional for the user to provide detailed social network information like linkedin connections and recommendations.

If you create a listing on our site, you will need to provide us your paypal email address or register with Amazon.com as a seller so that we can accept payments on your behalf. Amazon.com only provides a token to us and no other personal information is transferred to us by Amazon.com.

If you sell an item Paypal/Amazon will provide us with the shipping address of the buyer, the amount of the transaction and the phone number of the buyer. We will transfer these details to you via email.

If you purchase a listing on our site, Paypal/Amazon will provide us with your shipping address, amount of the transaction and your phone number. We will only share this information with the seller so that the item can be shipped to you. We do not have access to your payment information like credit/debit card or bank account etc.

Cookies

TrueGether saves some cookies to remember your recently viewed items, your location and your search queries. You must have cookies enabled to use this site. No personally identifiable information (e-mail address, name, etc.) is collected with the cookies that we set. We do not store your login/password etc in cookies. Accepting cookies while on the TrueGether.com site will not put the user at risk for marketing to other sites.

*Different browsers have different cookie settings. With Netscape, you can ask the browser to allow, warn you, or completely disable cookies. Internet Explorer has an additional feature where you can specify different settings for different security zones. You can choose to allow Web sites to create cookies for you in your "trusted sites" (like [Organization]), to warn you before you create them in your local Intranet zone, and to give you an option to never allow them in a "restricted zone." See the "Help" section of your particular browser for more information on working with cookies.

Web Statistics

We use Google Analytics to collect aggregate information about the browsers and operating systems etc that our users use. This information is not personally identifiable in anyway.

Sharing

We will not share your information in aggregate or otherwise with any individual or organization. This information will be used for the functionality of the site itself only.

Links

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that TrueGether.com does not claim any responsibility for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

Security

This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information, and we have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

Share with a friend

If users elect to use our "Share with a Friend" function, we ask them for the friend's name and e-mail address. TrueGether.com may automatically send friends a one-time e-mail message inviting them to visit the site. TrueGether.com stores this information temporarily for the sole purpose of sending this one-time message.

Updates

We may also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members will be able to to unsubscribe from such announcements. We communicate with users to provide requested services and to discuss issues relating to their accounts via e-mail or phone. You will be unable to opt out of an occasional administrative email as long as you have an account with us.

Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our home page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
